{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Playground \u0026 Swing Set Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40232/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40232,"taskName":"Outdoor Play Equipment - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair or Maintain Outdoor Play Equipment","xmTaskDescriptor":"Playground \u0026 Swing Set Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1720,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Outdoor Play playground Equipment playhouses","textMessagingName":"Repr Play Equip","rolloverLongDesc":"These firms inspect, maintain, rejuvenate \u0026 repair outdoor children's play equipment. Typically have expert knowledge about maintenance issues \u0026 have access to the specialized connecting hardware, anchoring systems \u0026 other parts.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes cleaning, treating, tightening, repairs, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Maintain Outdoor Play Equipment.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Playground \u0026 Swing Set Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Repair Playset \u0026 Outdoor Equipment","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":54,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Outdoor Play Equipment Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Outdoor Play Equipment - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Outdoor Play Equipment Project","urlName":"Outdoor-Play-Equipment-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Playground \u0026 Swing Set Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Outdoor,Play,playground,Equipment,playhouses,set,swing,swingset,playsets","emcCategoryOid":-12053,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":539,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40232/":{"taskOID":40232,"originalTaskOID":40232,"setID":539,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4944,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Needing Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What piece of equipment needs service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4726,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Platform/levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform/levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5370,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Rock-climbing walls","answerDisplayText":"Rock-climbing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4950,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service does it need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5192,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair","answerDisplayText":"Repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5439,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Routine maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Routine maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3213,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Initial installation","answerDisplayText":"Initial installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaned and coated","answerDisplayText":"Cleaned and coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4944,"questionDisplayText":"Equipment Needing Service","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What piece of equipment needs service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4726,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Platform/levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform/levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5370,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Rock-climbing walls","answerDisplayText":"Rock-climbing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6225,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Swings/gliders","answerDisplayText":"Swings/gliders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5780,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Slide","answerDisplayText":"Slide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3909,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Monkey bars","answerDisplayText":"Monkey bars","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3438,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Ladders","answerDisplayText":"Ladders","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4762,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Poles","answerDisplayText":"Poles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4726,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Platform/levels","answerDisplayText":"Platform/levels","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4731,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Playhouse","answerDisplayText":"Playhouse","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5423,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Ropes","answerDisplayText":"Ropes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5414,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Roof/canopy","answerDisplayText":"Roof/canopy","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6481,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Trapezes","answerDisplayText":"Trapezes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5353,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Rides","answerDisplayText":"Rides","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5370,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Rock-climbing walls","answerDisplayText":"Rock-climbing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5477,"answerDisplaySequence":13,"answerText":"Sand box","answerDisplayText":"Sand box","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":14,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4950,"questionDisplayText":"Service Needed","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of service does it need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5192,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair","answerDisplayText":"Repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5439,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Routine maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Routine maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3213,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Initial installation","answerDisplayText":"Initial installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaned and coated","answerDisplayText":"Cleaned and coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5192,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Repair","answerDisplayText":"Repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5439,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Routine maintenance","answerDisplayText":"Routine maintenance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3213,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Initial installation","answerDisplayText":"Initial installation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1418,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Cleaned and coated","answerDisplayText":"Cleaned and coated","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}